Look at us all crossing the same way.
I'm so bummed that I'm not hugging y'all.
I know it's hard.
Oh man it's so hard and I feel so rude.
It's such a southern thing for me to do, but I'm feeling a little under the weather, so I don't wanna get y'all sick.
We appreciate it.
[Kelly] Congrats season five was announced. Kelly：
And speaking of sickness, I don't mean to bring it up, but you got, like, really ill last season, right?
Yes I was like-
[Kelly] Like hospitalized. Kelly：
Yeah, I was in the ICU for quite a bit with sepsis.
It was just World Sepsis Day actually.
So just bringing awareness.
Oh wow that picture (laughing).
Well that's, as you can see, Paul Foreman who's in the show with me and plays my boyfriend on the show, was really there with me every step of the way.
And then I came straight into filming with you both.
And it was quite a challenging thing.
It's honestly, this press tour has been a really good way for me to process and recover.
And to kind of come to terms with it.
So I'm appreciative.
[Philippine] It was bad. Philippine：
It wasn't just a little thing, so we were really scared.
But I think when you came back, everyone was just like, "Whatever you need, however much time."
We were so excited to have her back.
But it was having her back in whatever way she was willing and able to be.
And I think you, I mean, God, she just killed it this season.
Well, I will say having strong women with me on set and really being the ones to say, "Do you need a second?
How are you doing?
Are you okay?
I'm gonna check in." "
Because we come to set and we have our hair and makeup and our stilettos on and it looks like it's all okay.
Especially to have a soul sister who's very much in tune with what I am going through.
It's an amazing cast, it's an amazing cast.
I gotta ask this too 'cause I feel like I've been having this conversation a lot with my girlfriends specifically lately.
What do you feel like is...
I feel like adult relationships, like once you start having friendships in that way, it's not only more meaningful, but I think it's more real.
Do you feel like that?
Especially when you're growing up in the industry, having relationships in the industry, has that helped y'all?
I think it's when you meet an adult as an adult, you're meeting who they are now, not who they're hopefully or maybe gonna become.
So if you connect as an adult, you are connecting on a different level.
And also without preconceived notions of the past.
There's no judgment of who you were once before.
Yeah and you're choosing in a different way.
Not as a kid, not by instinct, not because we wanna play doll together, but-
[Kelly] Yeah, it's not 'cause you're mom's were friends and you had to have a play date. Kelly：
We're choosing in a different way, which makes it kind of...
Yeah, they get me through it, too.
I think my adult female friendships specifically.
Yeah and there's different experiences and you've experienced things that you can tell us about.
Yeah, totally.
And I don't know, it's really wonderful to have cross generational friendships.
[Lily] I believe it's really important. Lily：
See that's alive and well in the music world.
Like we're all different ages.
So in the music world it's always like that.
So since I was 19 I've always grown up around just so many different ages of people and I love that.
I think there's so much expertise in that from the other generation, but also there's so much creativity that comes from that.
Yes, the best kind of friendship.
So it's hard to believe but, 'cause you have just such an amazing voice and I just found out you did Kelly-, karaoke for the first...
I called it Kelly-oke.
Hey no, but it was Kelly-oke!
I just owned it.
No, you did karaoke for the first time recently?
While we were filming.
'cause I had-
How have you done karaoke before?
Because, I don't know if you experienced this, but I love to have a heart to heart in the corner during karaoke because the people expect you to sound good and you're usually not in a condition to sound very good.
[Lily] There's so much pressure! Lily：
[Kelly Clarkson] I get up there and do rap songs. Kelly Clarkson：
I hadn't been out 'cause I was recovering and trying to stay healthy and at the very end of it someone who works on my team, Nikki, she was like, "I'm at an Irish pub in Rome right now.
" And we had just wrapped the scene.
I was like, "I'll meet up with you."
And it was a karaoke bar and it was all these bachelor and bachelorette parties, and they're like, "Let's sing-."
I was like, "Let's sing "Since U Been Gone" by Kelly Clarkson.
[Kelly] You did mine? Kelly：
Mine was your first...
Guys, "Since U Been Gone," "Breakaway," all of those are the best karaoke songs.
And it's a release, and you know all the lyrics.
Well I don't pick those, so yeah.
Could you imagine?
I'd look like such a tool.
I'm actually gonna do it just to be funny.
But they would be like, "That girl does it just like her.
Oh my God I wonder..." "
Oh my God, no I just found it amazing.
I feel like you probably grew up singing a lot.
So I was like, "How is that her first time?"
And that's amazing.
I love that it was "Since U Been Gone."
First and only.
Well Lily, speaking of live performances, you're about to make-, is it your West End debut?
I'm also told it's fine to be nervous 'cause I'm also very nervous.
Yeah, it means it matters.
But it's written by Bess Wohl who is the playwright, actually, who wrote Ashley's play that I saw right before the world shut down in COVID, Grand Horizons.
And so we have that in common.
She's wonderful.
And Lynette Linton, who runs the Bush Theater in London, is doing it.
And it's just myself and Álvaro Morte.
So it's a two person, 90 minute, no intermission, just going in deep water.
Yeah, well let's do a few commercials and pay the bills, people.
We've got Quentin helping us out.
Bonjour ladies, I teach French here in New York City.
My dad's French, my mom's American and that is why I don't speak with an accent.
Vive Emily à Paris! 《
And there's more with Kelly, Lily, Ashley, and Philippine after this.
(uplifting music plays) （
Welcome back.
We're here with Lily Collins, Philippine Leroy-Beaulieu and Ashley Park, the stars of the Netflix series Emily in Paris.
So, these characters are so well written.
But your character helped you realize kind of your own strength.
Is this true?
Yeah, yeah.
'cause she's very brave.
She's very-, she has an armor, but she's also very vulnerable.
And thanks to Darren, you know, his female characters are so whole.
They have a very masculine and very feminine energy.
[Kelly] Which we all do. Kelly：
Exactly.
But he balances it in a beautiful way.
That's why all his characters are so strong.
All his female characters are so strong.
So it's thanks to him.
Even the sexiness.
Yes!
Ma'am, I think you're bringing that by your self.
But, so, what's up with your characters this season?
I just love this season that Emily is not afraid to be more vulnerable.
I think she, it took her finding a safe, protected space in order to really feel the feelings and be able to articulate them.
And this season we get to see Emily in a more tailored, monochromatic wardrobe so that she can express more with her words.
Whereas season one it was very expressive on her wardrobe.
Colorful.
And a bit more type A in a box, emotionally.
And so I like that juxtaposition and it's taught me more and more about, you know, asking for help as a strength, not a weakness.
And it's okay to know when you've failed.
But not seeing it as a failure, just seeing it as a stepping stone.
So I was really happy that we got to explore more of that this season.
And it's exciting to change it up.
What about your character?
Well, I think all around it's, you know, we've been with these characters for four seasons, now.
And so it feels like higher stakes and, like, deeper layering all around.
And I think that for Mindy especially, we see her now in this, in a really adult kind of friendship and relationship.
We were talking about these adult friendships before.
Of this unconditional support.
And I think that we really kind of see Mindy have to reconcile if she's- see if she's gonna be able to reconcile her past with who she is now who she wants to be in the future.
That was vague.
No, no.
You know what, it's all very relatable.
It's so funny 'cause you would look at the show, especially aesthetically and you go, not relatable, I'm never gonna look like that.
But messaging wise there are some very relatable themes going on, which I think that's why-.
Congrats again on season five.
Like, the show is doing so well.
And I think 'cause people do relate to it.
But you shot in Rome and this is your hometown, right?
Yes.
I was raised there.
Was that cool?
Yeah, of course it's cool.
She went from like Sylvie to 'Sylvie'.
Do you get to film there often?
No, it was my first time filming there.
No, I shot Italy, but, like, Milano and Ancona, but never in Rome.
And after this horrible winter we had in Paris, suddenly it was like breath of light, fresh air.
It's like a hug.
You know, tenderness.
[Kelly] Best pasta ever. Kelly：
Philippine, you said you still cherish lessons from your mom and your grandmother and I read a little bit of you talking about them. Philippine，
My grandmother was a really, really elegant woman until the end, the very end.
And I thought her elegance, her way of wanting to be always perfect, kept her alive in a way.
And I thought it was like kind of cute and, more than cute.
It was wonderful.
And then my mom was a jewelry designer, knitwear and accessories and jewelry for 20 years.
And she was a beautiful woman.
So I looked up to them like incredible examples.
Also a bit oppressive in a way, but beautiful.
You had to look up to them.
I wanna grow and be that kind of tree, you know?
That's...
[Kelly] Yeah. Kelly：
You are, congratulations.
You have achieved it.
So are there any shows that kind of stuck out to you?
Because there's a lot of meaningful topics that y'all do cover.
But any that kind of stuck out to you?
Sylvie trusting Emily more and more, which is something that, trust for me is a tricky one.
[Kelly] You had to earn it, you know? Kelly：
And I'm really about loyalty, so when people betray me I'm like desperate.
So, so yeah, her trusting Emily more and more was like, oh.
It was a really interesting thing.
And how, you know, trust to the point to say, 'you're going to take over the office in Rome,' which, it's a big move 'cause she wanted to stay in Rome, obviously.
So, you know.
But that trust for me was an important thing.
You have any that stick out to you?
You know what's funny?
Good answer!
Good answer.
Whenever we get applause, that sticks out to me.
[Kelly] It's like family feud. Kelly：
When you said, like, moments, it's so funny because I was trying to think of them and I remember a time when we were filming when I could count on my hands 'Oh yeah.
These are the amount of scenes that I've had in the apartment with Emily'. "
And then now there's been so much history and there's so many ups and downs, you know, I love their little debrief sessions.
And it feels very much like it echoes and mirrors us in real life, too.
I can't count how many times we've been there for each other.
We've listened to each other, had a heart to heart.
And I love that.
It really feels like, like they're home in each other, now.
So it's funny to try to pinpoint a moment.
'cause I'm like, 'when did that conversation happen?
Because she was crying.
Were we even on set?
Yeah!
I love that answer.
Well, okay, so Lily, the last thing we have is something in common.
I heard this about you and I was like, I never really heard of anyone doing this in Hollywood.
And, 'cause usually people are very proper.
You, at a fancy party, as well have just totally jumped in a pool.
Fully clothed.
Yeah, I did, I did.
Oh, there we go.
[Ashley] There we go. Ashley：
That was like a couple weeks ago.
[Kelly] So here's my question. Kelly：
I jumped in because I was dragged to a party I didn't wanna go to and I was like, I'm bored.
And so me and my whole band just jumped in.
[Lily] Oh, fun. Lily：
It was not our scene.
And we made it our scene, you know, tried to find the light.
But why did you do it?
Because it was a 'why not?' moment.
I don't even know.
I think it was, I was like, 'who should we push in the pool?'
And she was like-,
You started that.
I remember.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She was like, 'I don't think we should push anyone, but I'm gonna jump in it.'
And I've never felt, I was like, 'I'm a true beta.'
'cause I watched her jump in the pool and I was like, 'me too, I must go too.'
It was at the house of one of our friends, but yeah, someone who is technically one of our bosses at Netflix and it was at his house and it was his first dinner party and it was like, we were sitting there and I was like, 'this pool is so pretty, I feel like something needs to happen.
' But I was like looking at my clothes and I remember looking at Samuel and I said, "Samuel, if I do something, can I wear your jacket as a dress?"
And he was like, "Yes."
And so I was like, look to Ashley.
And I went, "Just pull your camera out."
She's like, "What?
And so then I just, like, jumped up from the table and did it.
And I thought, 'no one, I'm like the least likely at this table to do this.
And I just feel like I gotta just do it'.
[Kelly] It feels good. Kelly：
And then I did it.
I was like, this is a best night ever.
I was filming you.
There's something about, like, the child in you.
Because my kids, when they get to a pool, they're like, for some reason they just, it's more exciting if they're jumping in in clothes they shouldn't be in.
There's something about the child in us.
No, I was wearing a Saint Laurent dress.
It couldn't go into water.
I'm sorry.
But you cheered us on.
You're super classy.
Look, I did jump in in an outfit that was not a gown.
I will say that, but yeah.
I didn't, I think the driver hated us because we got in and we were all soaked.
We all had to-
The host of the party, he lent us all his sweats.
So.
I mean we literally ended up leaving in, like, sweatsuits.
I had a Netflix sweatsuit as I left the party.
You like, stole swag.
I like it.
Yeah, I still have it.
I was like, this is too cute.
I'm not returning it.
It's in the wash.
Everybody give it up for the ladies of Emily in Paris.
You can see all episodes of the show on Netflix.
Also, we have an exclusive.
Bath and Body Works is teaming up with Emily in Paris to bottle up the essence of the show's most iconic scenes. Bath and Body Works
And while the limited edition collection doesn't officially launch until November, everyone, bless you, everyone in the audience is getting a $200 Bath and Body Works gift card to shop.